iconocast.com 2007-05-09

# Iconocast privacy policy

  |    
---|---  
  |    

ADVERTISING BY ICONOCAST

[**Optimism, Happiness, Self Esteem, Creativity, Competency, Achieve Intrinsic Motivation; visit www.motivationbook.com**](http://www.motivationbook.com/)

**[Iconocast is about learning and teaching without borders; we offer eMarketing, Internet Advertising, Internet Marketing, Search Engine Optimization, Search Engine Marketing, Online Branding, and eMarketing News Services.](http://www.iconocast.com/index.html)**  
  
## **Our commitment to your privacy, security and our Privacy Policy**

_**Your privacy is of outmost importance to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.**_

### How We Protect the Security of Your Information

For your privacy, we employ the latest encryption and security technology and fraud detection techniques in all areas of iconocast.com where you provide us with personal or account information. This is done to protect you from unauthorized use of the information you are sending to our server. To make sure you have the latest security features on your browser, please download and install the latest version of your favorite browser, Microsoft Internet Explorer or Netscape Communicator. Please note, for privacy purposes, once you give us any information relating to you, it is stored on a highly secure server that is not accessible via the Internet. All these is for your own privacy. Your privacy is important for all of us to build trust and make sure our business is sound.

**What Information Do We Collect from You and How Do We Use It?**

**_Personal Information._**

We do not share e-mail names collected on our site for purposes of permitting other companies to market to you through e-mail. Providing us your e-mail address will not result in your receiving unsolicited commercial e-mail from any third party.  

**_Information From Children._** We do not direct our Web site to children.

**_Transmission Errors or Unauthorized Acts._** Although we will use all reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. 

**_Required by Law._** In extreme cases, where required by law, we may be forced to release information regarding our customers to permit the investigation of credit card fraud, illegal use of the Internet, or cases of misconduct on our Web site.

**_Other Web Sites._** This Privacy Policy only addresses iconocast.com and our information gathering practices. To the extent that you disclose personal information to other Web sites, you are subject to other Web sites’ privacy policies. We encourage you to review a third party Web sites’ privacy policies before you disclose any personal information which may be collected by a third party.

**_Change of Ownership._** In the event that either of our Web sites become owned or controlled by other individuals or entities, the information we have collected may be transferred to such party or parties. To the maximum extent allowed by law, however, such individuals or entities will be required to use information only in accordance with the provisions of this privacy policy.

We do not share any of this information with outside parties. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. We might use the information you provide to improve our website. However, we absolutely do not use any identifying and aggregate information to share with advertisers. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

### **We do not relate or work with children; however, we are most committed To Any Children's Privacy. No person under the age of 18 is allowed to do business with us.**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. 

## **How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at **info1(at)iconocast.com**

First Law of Branding

Second Law of Branding

**Third Law of Branding**

**Fourth Law of Branding**

**Fifth Law of Branding**

**Sixth Law of Branding**

**Seventh Law of Branding**

**Eighth Law of Branding**

**Ninth Law of Branding**

**Tenth Law of Branding**

****Eleventh Law of Branding****

****Twelfth Law of Branding****
